ASHLEY E. NGUYEN smashflashtech@gmail.com

FULL-SCACK ENGINEER

Los Angeles, CA

www.smashflashtech.com (213) 290-3296

SKILLS

Javascript | Python HTML5 | CSS3 | GITHUB/GIT EJS | React | Node.JS EXPRESS | MONGODB | FLask SQL ALCHEMY | SEQUELIZE POSTGRESOL | DJANGO

PROJECTS

Virtual Beer Pong

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

Automated Stimulus Display and Data Collection (ASDDC)

REACT | SQL ALCHEMY FLASK | PYTHON

Leafy Ledger

EXPRESS | EJS NODE.JS | POSCGRESQL

certificates

General Assembly
LOS Angeles (Remote)

December 2020

Software Engineering BOARD CERCIFIED BEHAVIOR ANALYSC

May 2016

Certificate#: 1-16-22669

EDUCACION

THE CHICAGO SCHOOL OF Professional psychology

Ph.D. Psychology, Behavior Analysis Specialization

August 2017 - Present GPA: 4.0

M.S. Applied Behavior Analysis

October 2015

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, BERKELEY

B.A. Psychology

May 2008

SUMMARY

Full-stack engineer pivoting from 12 years of behavior analytic experience collecting & analyzing data and making data-driven decisions to solve problems, implement solutions, and audit success in the context of Human Services and graduate level education. Seeking an opportunity to apply these skills in the tech industry by building applications that produce measurable improvement in performance and quality of life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Los Angeles, CA (Remote)

Software Engineer Instructional Associate March 2021 - Present

- O Create controller and modify routes within Node.js framework to check if a user has reached or will exceed 10K lead upload limit and return & render error message to React front-end when true.
- O Develop logic to detect file size, quantity, and frequency of uploads and allow posts to PostgreSQL database or return & render error message when file size is exceeded maximum allowance or upload limit is reached.

General Assembly West Coast (Remote)

Software Engineer Instructional Associate January 2021 - April 2021

- O Facilitates acquisition of frontend & backend development technologies across two programming languages for a cohort of 30 students with 100% on track to graduate.
- O Audits lessons & provides feedback to students for 30+ pull requests per week.
- O Supports student project development using an Agile project management approach.

The Chicago School of Professional Psychology Adjunct Faculty August 2018 - October 2020

Los Angeles & Irvine, CA

- Established curriculum and associated experiential activities for Behavioral Assessments master level course used across three Southern CA campuses.
- O Led graduate students through hands-on application of behavioral technologies while providing instruction, modeling, constructive feedback, and performance evaluation across various Practicum skills & topics resulting in 100% pass rate.

Curriculum Development Collaborator

August 2019 - April 2020

Chicago, IL (Remote)

- O Developed curriculum and associated experiential activities for Behavioral Assessments bachelor level course for remote online instruction.
- O Audited course materials for final publication ensuring curriculum met educational standards and certification board requirements and ADA compliance leading to successful course publication by Fall 2020 semester.

Easterseals Southern California

Regional Trainer

May 2017 - September 2017

Southern California Counties

- O Analyzed complex skills and developed standardized training protocols enabling quality assurance competency checks for clinical and administrative performance.
- O Trained staff in crisis management and behavioral technologies using research-based methods leading to 100% pass rate.

Program Manager

June 2016 - May 2017

Los Angeles, CA

- O Evaluated data, summarized results, and recommended treatment options to stakeholders leading to continuation, termination, or graduation of services.
- O Supervised staff performance, provided training, assessed morale, and coordinated team building meetings leading to 100% retention of direct supervisees.